[{"answer": "I'm awesome, I feel great.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "Yeah, people have been loosing their lives now from this, where these kids around America.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "Have they been?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't make anything of it.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Oh yeah, you know, if I was on a robbing spree as I'm robbing somebody when I was a young kid I've done something like that but this is just for fun.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Have you ever, when you grew up on the streets of Brooklyn, would you ever have done something like that?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Why do people do it you think?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Healthcare, these people haven't been to the doctor in 20 years.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "What do you think the real cares and fears of the average American on the street are right now?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "This thing really, it just really went horrible, isn't it?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "If they can get the healthcare, but as of now it doesn't seem they can get it.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "I mean the idea behind it, would you be supportive of the idea of bringing millions of Americans into healthcare, who wouldn't otherwise be able to afford it?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Well, maybe as a President, I don't know what it takes to become a President.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Does it reduce his standing as a President?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well listen, we got to stop being involved with the knockout game.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Do you think that's a fair criticism from what you hear on the streets?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "YSON: It could be in Los Angeles.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Could be anywhere, right?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Listen, it was meant that way, that's why the jails are full of us.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "What do you do about it?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "White will have guns too.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Just more and more guns?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Hey, people go can do what they want to do in life and have nothing to do about what our community do.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "What is your view about that debate?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Oh wow, now it's pretty interesting.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "What is it like being Mike Tyson?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I'm just -- I'm very I don't want to say I'm a complete person by any means.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Your state of mind?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, like that as was explained earlier it's a struggle.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "How hard is it to keep that away?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "YSON: Hey.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Who do you feel like giving the most thanks to in your life?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I said this is a well done book.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "When you finished it, you read the final version what did you think?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Well, it haven't been difficult.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "How hard is it being for you to be that open?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "No it's not but the fact is that who is my father is -- whose been in my life for that period in time that I know was, you know Curly Kirkpatrick and that's why I always consider my father.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "That's not a subject of humor really is it?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "You know, this is where it's very tricky in this particular situation.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "They told that you've been doing, How important has it been for you to have that audience's reaction again to work out hear people cheering for you?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "There was a time when you were the most infamous fighter on the planet, the most dangerous guy out there and you played up to that, baddest man on the planet and so on.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "It's that the same feeling?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Money doesn't mean anything to me, I don't know that's just who I am.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "And if I can say to you now, look you can have money and success but you won't be recognized, would you take that option or is there a part of it that you like?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Hey, I'm just, anything I trust complicity is with my wife.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "How many people do you trust completely?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "You've been married only five years?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I'm extremely proud of that.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Are you proud of that?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Hey, I'm more than lucky, I'm just very grateful as well, you know, and it's just -- it was something I never dreamed that I'd be capable of doing.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Do you feel lucky that she came into your life?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Hey, I'm -- I can't live with myself so how do you think is going to be easy for somebody else to live with me if I'm really -- I'm very difficult to live with myself.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Are you difficult to be around?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Would you think you would have even made it out of your teenage years without your mother?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Hey, listen, that was partly for me, I don't know why would you that she was dead, how could that -- how could you enjoy that, you know, maybe that's my guilt of being a horrible son.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Why did you that?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Maybe it wasn't thanking her but maybe to tell and show that I love her, you know, but that's how my life has always been, by my love, you know.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Was it your way of thanking her or be it belatedly?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I don't know, we didn't have that relationship.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "Did you ever get the chance to tell her that you loved her?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "What would you, what would you -- if you had the chance to talk to her again, what would you say to her now at the stage of your life?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Not much.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "But, what did you learn about money?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Well, the younger kids do.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "When you go around the world, is that one of the things that most people not talked to you about, the Hangover?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Let me play the commercial.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "I was like your fan and stuff and most of the guys run around and ask me what was 2pac like?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Well it's great.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Are you okay?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "One way.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "So Mr. Rodman, roundtrip to North Korea?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "Shocked.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "That moment when you realized Mike Tyson has decided to eat your ear in the middle of a fight, what goes to your mind?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I was horrified.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "I mean, Lewis, when you were watching that, what did you think?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "So we're both sitting here.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "He did?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Yes, I did bite his leg.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Did you bite Lennox Lewis' leg?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "And you did get any chunk of it to keep or?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "When you see the video of you biting Holyfield's ear, what do you think?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "And you deserve the news?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Big time.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "So you're pleased about that?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Hey man, you can't imagine.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Do you get a lot of pleasure now from these young boxers that you're helping to mentor?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "All of them.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "All of them?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Haven't been getting arguments now.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "When was the last time?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "No time recently.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Because people must still tried on with you, right?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I will -- I don't know.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "How would you react if they did?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "I don't want to do it.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "But if you have to, you would?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Do you still work out a lot?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I got a book that's the history of warfare and the histories of all the generals and warfare.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "I mean I know you use to read lots of books and what kind of things you like to read?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Man, there's a lot of great other sports to, with a lot of great women athletes too.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Any sportsman from other sports?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "YSON: No way.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "And was Ali the guy that you would love to have fought?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "If can now, would you ever get back in the ring?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Pretty much.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "You're done with that?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Would you fight Holyfield?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Well it is -- I'm not as young as I used to be.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Does that bother you?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Well I never thought about that, just being free again.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Everything that's happened to you that's in this extraordinary book?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I've never been that free before.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Why did you like it so much?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Actually she was four years old?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Hey, I used to -- this way, I used to feel like that when I was at the hospital where other people's children had died or was dying as my daughter died and I realized I don't have no exclusives of either pain and I have to handle it like everyone else handled it and try to be a better father for the children that I have living with me now and to the best of my ability and that's just what it is and that's all I can do, unless I can kill myself and deal with the pain that way and I don't think that's the best way to do it.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "How did you deal with it?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Hey listen, whatever situation arise I try to help them to the best of my ability.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "What do you say to them as a father?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well I (inaudible) was to be kind to them and treat them nice and yeah so, it's just difficult situation, you know, I mean dealing with children with matters like that, matters of the heart and I try to give them the best advice possible they can with those situations and I just hope that he listens to me because he's going to make his decisions.", "docId": "131127pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "And what do you say to him about that?", "qSentId": 618}]